<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Rookie Reverser</title><link>https://kalilistic.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Rookie Reverser</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kalilistic.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>learning c: objects, functions, and types</title><link>https://kalilistic.github.io/posts/learning-c-objects-functions-types/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kalilistic.github.io/posts/learning-c-objects-functions-types/</guid><description>Slightly belated, but here is my second blog post on learning c. I&amp;rsquo;m not going to exhaustively list what I&amp;rsquo;m learning as I&amp;rsquo;m not sure a regurgitation of the source material will be that interesting. So instead, I&amp;rsquo;ll share points of interest that stood out to me.
Preprocessor Directives The &amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo; application has two preprocessor directives at the top. #include &amp;lt;stdio.h&amp;gt; #include &amp;lt;stdlib.h&amp;gt; These behave in your code as if you&amp;rsquo;ve replaced them with the contents of the specified module.</description></item><item><title>learning c</title><link>https://kalilistic.github.io/posts/learning-c/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kalilistic.github.io/posts/learning-c/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to start learning C. I&amp;rsquo;ve always worked with higher-level languages that have abstracted away certain concepts like pointers and garbage collection. I will start this by reading and completing the exercises in Effective C by Robert C. Seacord. The reviews describe this as a modern K&amp;amp;R, often held up as the standard of programming books.
I&amp;rsquo;ll make a post at least every few chapters to share my progress.</description></item><item><title>a statement of purpose</title><link>https://kalilistic.github.io/posts/a-statement-of-purpose/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kalilistic.github.io/posts/a-statement-of-purpose/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m inspired to try my hand at blogging. I&amp;rsquo;ve recently renewed my efforts to learn reverse engineering. I&amp;rsquo;ll use this platform to help organize my thoughts, hold myself accountable, and maybe even solicit feedback from my dear readers.
What am I hoping to accomplish?
Better understand how the software I write works. Build more compelling mods for some of my favorite games. Solve crackmes/CTFs. Learn something new and have some fun.</description></item></channel></rss>